Now I'll show the second tool
in Vizai.
With it you can take
that texture from your supplier
and turn it into a seamless texture.
And the best part
is that you can adjust everything,
from the size to the grout
and other details.
For this example,
I'll go to the Portobello
website and download 4 textures
of the same
porcelain tile.
Each image has small variations,
and that makes the texture look
much more realistic.
And of course,
you can also upload just one
image to the plugin,
if you prefer.
Applied the texture to
your project and still need some
adjustments?
Just select the texture
in SketchUp and come back to adjust
everything in the plugin.
And remember,
these tools tab features
are completely free,
you can use them as much as you want,
without spending any of
your credits.